(Penny:)Oh, okay. Well, I was hoping, um,
you could do me a favor.
(Stuart:)Sure, yeah. Name it.
(Penny:)I'm kind of responsible
for Sheldon missing Stan Lee.
I really wanna make it up to him.
I was hoping...
...you could give me his number
so I can arrange for them to meet.
(Stuart:)Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't have his phone number.
(Penny:)Damn. All right. Thank you.
STUART:
Mm-hm.
(Sheldon:)Wait.
(Stuart:)I have his address.
(Penny:)Really? Great.
(Stuart:)But I can't give it to you.
(Penny:)-Then why did you tell me you had it?
-I don't know. Just chatting.
(Stuart:)You're looking at a guy who could very well
get stood up by a stray cat tonight.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, Stuart. Thanks anyway.
STUART:
Mm-hm.
(Sheldon:)Wait.
(Penny:)-Yeah?
-Maybe we can make a deal.
(Penny:)What kind of deal?
(Stuart:)I will give you the address if you go
to my cousin's wedding with me.